[
  {
    "question": "What does a singleton do?",
    "options": [
      "create a object accessibly only by that class",
      "prevent security issues by sharing variables publicly",
      "create a single global access class"
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a good example of a singleton in unity",
    "options": [
      "the whole project",
      "controlling what the user/player can do",
      "game manager",
      "as an interface to a library"
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is a CON for using a singleton ",
    "options": [
      "memory management issues",
      "concurrency issues",
      "limited to only one instance",
      "There are no cons"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is a PRO for using a singleton ",
    "options": [
      "good for memory management",
      "no concurrency issues",
      "easy to debug",
      "There are no pros"
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is an alternative to using singleton",
    "options": [
      "toolbar",
      "toolkit",
      "toolbox",
      "dynamic"
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Would you use a Singleton for the Music Manager Object?",
    "options": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Would you use a Singleton for the Player Object?",
    "options": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },


  {
    "question": "Would you use a private or public constructor to instantiate a singleton ",
    "options": [
      "private",
      "public"
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Using Singletons is good for testing, because you can easily re-use them",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How does android avoid the use of singletons ",
    "options": [
      "Static Variables",
      "Using an SQLlite database to manage data",
      "Passing the context as a parameter almost everywhere"
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Sometimes, when using a singleton we can find problems with ________",
    "options": [
      "concurrency",
      "speed",
      "gui",
      "access"
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were to use a Singleton on a Quiz, what would you use it for",
    "options": [
      "To display information",
      "To keep the score between questions",
      "To store the questions",
      "To randomize the questions"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  }
]